now i get it we're all like okay if we can't vote for joe and we can't vote for trump who
we gonna vote for and i see a lot of y'all saying marianne williamson marianne williamson
now i done interviewed this lady and i was not impressed by her but some of y'all was really
still holding on and i hope that this video quiets y'all once and for all from continuing
to act like this white lady is gonna come and white save us she not read her book and call it a
day well israel is not an occupying force in gaza israelis can't even go into gaza
that is marianne williamson who some have been touting as the presidential candidate that will
save america and i just have to say that clip displays why i fear that my career in social
commentary and advocacy will only go so far i lack the restraint that it takes to sit there calmly
while being gaslighted by somebody who's asking for my vote lauren stated a fact that the occupation
of gaza has been an issue long before october 7th and marianne's response was there before october
7th excuse me she then proceeds to deny that an occupation has even taken place and agrees that
this phrase is equivalent to calling for genocide i'm telling you i couldn't have sat there quietly
i could not because my response would have been ma'am it's clear that you are aligned with other
aspiring politicians who co-opt social justice and revolution when it's convenient for your campaign
all the while being too pussy to actually stand on the principles that you claim to hold i would also
let her know that this is why democratic candidates are losing support even amongst leftists because we
recognize that though y'all say the right things when we really dig into your politic you're just as
untrustworthy as the others and i know that marianne has been calling for a ceasefire i've been seeing
people say that we can't expect perfection from our candidates but we're not asking for perfection
just a candidate who's willing to address these issues in a way that's actually impactful and that
represents the people and most of these motherfuckers aren't even willing to acknowledge the issues in
their entirety so how can they address them she nailed it 10 out of 10 no notes sis no notes
yes
you